<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home</title>
    <description>Central place for info about me</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>What is Software Engineering</title>
        <description>
          
          Lately I’ve been interested in what is software engineering, by likening it to aspects of other disciplines. This is primarily written within the context of this blog post as well as a general response to the initial question. To lightly summarize, much of the post discusses various models of software...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019-05-02-swe/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019-05-02-swe/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Instagram's Magic Spell</title>
        <description>
          
          Mirror mirror on the wall, show me the best of them all. Whenever I’m asked if I’m on Instagram, I find it hard to reply with something concrete - so I usually go with “I do, but I don’t”. What does that even mean?! Not sure, but I’d like to...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019-04-15-magic/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019-04-15-magic/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Design Course Debrief</title>
        <description>
          
          Beginning in January, I was involved in taking an introductory Human-Centered Design course, provided by +Acumen and IDEO.org. Going into it, I had a belief that design is central to many creative processes, and was looking to dive a bit more in-depth into the whole process. My only previous experience...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019-03-18-designDebrief/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019-03-18-designDebrief/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Résumés</title>
        <description>
          
          Origins (and future) of the Résumé While applying for jobs recently, I’ve been spending lots of time writing and rewriting résumés but it’s hard to evaluate if there’s even much of a payoff for that time invested, and the feeling that this short, almost meaningless document is the only thing...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019-03-17-resumes/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019-03-17-resumes/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sample Sales</title>
        <description>
          
          I check out NYC samples sales occasionally - a good resource has been The Choosy Beggar. I had a problem with the way the site separated each sale post and their respective maps, meaning I’d go through multiple clicks back and forth to view each location, and couldn’t plan my...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019-02-06-ss-project/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019-02-06-ss-project/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Shutdowns</title>
        <description>
          
          A rising indicator for how ingrained a service or company is within society could be its usage in language, otherwise known as mind share. I’m sure this is not a new idea, but it seems to be the mark for modern successful companies - aka “unicorns”, with terms that include...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019-02-06-shutdowns/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019-02-06-shutdowns/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
